http://www.translatorsbase.com/privacy.aspx

Privacy Policy
Translatorsbase wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy and has displayed
its privacy statement for your review:
What personally identifiable information
of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through
What choices are available to you
regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?
The kind of security procedures
that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under
(Name of the Company) control
How you can correct any inaccuracies
in the information.
If you have any concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Translatorsbase's
privacy administrator by email at service@Translatorsbase.com
The purpose of our privacy statement is to make our clients aware of our dedication
to preserve Translatorsbase customer privacy. As our services require us to collect client
information, Translatorsbase has created this privacy statement in order to communicate
our information gathering practices and procedures.
Changes to this Privacy Statement: We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement,
and will publish notification on our web site no less than 30 days before the statement
modifications take effect.
, email: service@Translatorsbase.com
is the organizations collecting the Personally Identifiable Information and/or Third
Party Personally Identifiable Information through the Site.
When a user contracts Translatorsbase services, the user is required to provide such
information as their name, company name, address, phone number, e-mail address,
product selection, and billing information. It is possible that we will also ask
for additional information such as company industry, number of employees, etc.,
at the time our service is contracted or if interest in our services is expressed.
It is optional for customers to provide this additional information, and users may
choose not to do so when they activate services with Translatorsbase or request information
on our services.
When Translatorsbase captures user information upon sign-up, we use the client information
to activate the customer account. Once a client has signed up with Translatorsbase, future
mailing may periodically be sent out to the Translatorsbase client base, introducing
new products, product updates, and important Translatorsbase news and information. Our
users and clients have the option of receiving the Translatorsbase company newsletter.
Should a client choose to receive the newsletter via e-mail, we will not distribute
the user e-mail address for any other purpose than the sending of our newsletter
or other Translatorsbase service information. If a user would like to cease receiving
the newsletter or other promotional e-mail correspondence from Translatorsbase, they
may send an e-mail request to service@Translatorsbase.com
and immediately be removed from future mailings. Translatorsbase requires a valid, working
e-mail address upon account setup in order to send our client account information
details, including a welcome packet, and account username and password.
Translatorsbase does not disclose any user/customer information to any third party, other
than what we explicitly state upon account activation or as detailed in our Terms
of Use. Billing and financial information is required upon account activation for
Translatorsbase to bill for services rendered. Translatorsbase will only use this billing
information to verify the validity of the account, and bill for Translatorsbase services.
When Translatorsbase bills for services rendered, a third-party processing company is
used to charge customer credit cards and collect payment. This third-party is used
only to process credit card charges, and does not store or distribute customer credit
card or billing information.
Additionally, the Translatorsbase website may contain content from third-party content
providers, but these content providers neither receive nor distribute Translatorsbase
user or customer information, nor do they receive user or customer information from
Translatorsbase.
Translatorsbase provides a service where our customers upload and store their data on
Translatorsbase servers and equipment. Translatorsbase does not review, edit, disseminate,
or use this data in any way, except as may be required by law, or as outlined in
our Terms of Use. Customer data or records may be viewed from time to time to handle
a technical support request that is initiated by the client, or to resolve any other
problem or technical issue. Additionally, we reserve the right to disclose your
personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that
disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding,
court order, or legal process served on our Company or Web site, or if there is
a suspected Terms of Use violation.
Translatorsbase users are solely and individually responsible for maintaining the privacy
and confidentiality of their own data, as well as their usernames and passwords.
Translatorsbase may collect information from visitors to the Translatorsbase web site. Most
commonly, we may collect the Internet addresses of Translatorsbase site visitors. We
use the information that we log from the Translatorsbase website to both improve our
services, and help troubleshoot possible Translatorsbase website problems. We may also
analyze non-identifying statistics that we collect from website visitor usage, and
provide this data to qualified third parties.
Cookies
Security protocols put into operation by Translatorsbase are determined by encrypted
session Ids and dynamic data. Should you select to activate the Translatorsbase "Remember
Me" feature, we will use a "cookie" that contains partial or full authentication
information depending on your preference. The cookie will reside on your local system.
Further, We use a third party to provide statistical analysis regarding our users
use of the www.translatorsbase.com
web site and may set cookies in order to gather the information
needed to perform their statistical analysis. The information collected by the third
party cookies does not contain any personal information or can be linked back to
any individual user.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement,
and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not
linked to personally identifiable information.
Links
Our web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Translatorsbase.
are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage
our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements
of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This
privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site or the
Translatorsbase application.
Surveys
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation
in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether
or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information
and demographic information. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring
or improving the use and satisfaction of this site or of the Translatorsbase application.
Security
Translatorsbase has chosen to implement the latest technology that allows for the highest
levels of Internet security that are possible today. If you are accessing our site
with 4.0 versions or higher of Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator
browsers, your information is encrypted and authenticated, using Secure Socket Layer
(SSL) technology. The SSL systems provide complete data security for you and your
users, and the authentication ensures that your valuable content is available only
to registered users, and is not accessible to unwanted parties. Each registered
user is provided with a unique username and password. Each time a user logs onto
Translatorsbase.com or Directfreelance.com website, he can only be authenticated
and allowed access using the correct username and password that has been assigned.
A session is issued for the purpose of capturing encrypted authentication data for
the length of the session. Neither the username nor the password is included in
the session. Security protocols put into operation by Translatorsbase are determined
by encrypted session Ids and dynamic data. Should you select to activate the Translatorsbase
"Remember Me" feature, we will use a "cookie" that contains partial or full authentication
information depending on your preference. The cookie will reside on your local system.
Opt-Out Policy
Translatorsbase offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information
provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering Services,
you change your mind about receiving information from us, send us a request specifying
your new choice. Simply send your request to service@Translatorsbase.com
Correcting and Updating Your Information
To update billing information or discontinue the Service please email
Wedding License
Our platform, Translatorsbase.com, is a translation marketplace where translators can create an online presence, apply for work, share knowledge and collaborate.
Useful Links
Find Work
Get Free Quotes
Our Rates
Resources
Translation Articles
Free Translation
Translation Rates
